Guide to the Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies records, 1966-2014 RL.11552
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Center Offices, 1969-2013
  - Office of Communications and Marketing (OCM), 1969-2013
    - OCM Media, 1980-2012
      - OCM Audiovisual, 1980-2012
        - U.S. Labor Issues: Looking to the Future Marketing video #2, 1997 Jan 27 (Box 149, Video-cassette RL11552-VHS-0030)
        - Unlabeled event - mix, Tape 1 moderator, Tape 2 left panel, Tape 3 right panel, undated; 4 items (Box 167, Video-cassette RL11552-Umatic-0009 - RL11552-Umatic-0012)
        - Unlabelled, undated (Box 160, Video-cassette RL11552-VHS-0067)
        - Unnatural Causes, Not Just a Paycheck, 2007 Sep 10 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0180)
        - Urban Teens, WETA, 1989 Jun 8 (Box 163, Video-cassette RL11552-Umatic-0001)
        - Video bus tour cd 1-5, undated; 5 items (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0002 - RL11552-OP-0006)
        - Wealth Gap, 2009 Jun 29 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0296)
        - White House exit interviews, Louis Martin, audio, 1980 Jun (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0364)
        - Why in the World - Black Politics, undated (Box 166, Video-cassette RL11552-Umatic-0007)
        - William T. Grant Foundation Youth Development Prize, 2003 (Box 161, Video-cassette RL11552-VHS-0081)
        - Witness to Freedom, 1995 Feb 1 (Box 149, Video-cassette RL11552-VHS-0029)
        - Witness to Freedom, 1995 Jan 3 (Box 161, Video-cassette RL11552-VHS-0077)
        - Witness to Freedom, undated (Box 148, Videotape RL11552-Bcam-0015)
        - WJLA News 7 Black Male Initiative, 1996 Jun 6 (Box 160, Video-cassette RL11552-VHS-0064)
        - WJLA TV News 7 South African Elections, 1994 Apr 19 (Box 160, Video-cassette RL11552-VHS-0062)
        - WKKF Devolution poll, 1999 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0401)
        - Worldnet 1268 - Euronet 553, 1989 June 13 (Box 149, Video-cassette RL11552-VHS-0007)
        - Youth Power Center, 2006 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0151)
        - Yvonne Scruggs - Tape 1, undated (Box 161, Video-cassette RL11552-VHS-0092)
      - OCM Audio
        Includes recordings of speeches, interviews, and conferences arranged alphabetically.
        - 1987 Annual dinner, 1987 Apr 8 (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0148)
        - 1988 Annual dinner (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0149)
        - 1994 Annual dinner, 1994 Mar 24 (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0150)
        - 1999 Annual dinner tape 1, 1999 Mar 23 (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0154)
        - 1999 Annual dinner tape 2, 1999 Mar 23 (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0155)
        - Afro-American press conference, 1988 Mar 15 (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0139)
        - Afro-Americans and the Evolution of a Living Constitution Tape 2, undated (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0127)
        - Afro-Americans and the Evolution of a Living Constitution Tape 4, undated (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0128)
        - Black Neighborhoods in Transition Side 3, 1983 Mar 1 (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0130)
        - Black Neighborhoods in Transition Sides 1 and 2, 1983 Mar 1 (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0129)
        - Board of Governors meeting, 1983 Mar 30 (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0142)
        - Carl Anthony interview, 2007 Jan 11 (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0138)
        - Constitutional Roots, Rights and Responsibilities Tape 2, undated (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0131)
        - Corporation forum, 1999 Mar 23 (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0153)
        - Democracy in Action: Great Louis Trichardt, undated (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0118)
        - Democracy in Action: Greater Lebowakgomo, undated (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0116)
        - Democracy in Action: Greater Tzaneen, undated (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0117)
        - Democracy in Action: Levubu-Shingwedzi, undated (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0115)
        - Democracy in Action: Thohoyandou, undated (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0114)
        - Dr. Louis Clark interview, tape 1-2, 1998 May 5; 2 items (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0135 - RL11552-CS-0136)
        - Economic Policy news conference, 1988 Sep 14 (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0140)
        - Eddie Williams interview, tape 1-4, 2004 Aug; 4 items (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0144 - RL11552-CS-0147)
        - Ernest Green interview, 2007 Jun 15 (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0137)
        - In the Tradition Pilot, undated (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0141)
        - Joint Center dinner, 1978 Mar 9 (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0143)
        - Joint Center tape 1-3 master, 2006 Apr 11; 3 items (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0132 - RL11552-CS-0134)
        - Klerksdorp Community News, undated (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0121)
        - Kroonstad Community News, 2000 Jan (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0119)
        - Local Government Transformation Programme, undated (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0113)
        - Open the Door to Democracy Qwaqwa TRC, undated (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0125)
        - Orkney/Kanana Community News, undated (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0122)
        - Paul Roux Community News, 2000 (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0120)
        - Phafogang Women's Training Network, undated (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0123)
        - Portfolio of State Issues Volume 3 No. 4, 1986 (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0126)
        - Tsebo Women's Training Network, undated (Box 172, Audio-cassette RL11552-CS-0124)
      - OCM Photographs, 1977-2013
        OCM photographs document the Joint Center events, meetings and dinners, and are arranged alphabetically.
        - 2005 Annual dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0279)
        - 2005 Dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0221)
        - 2008 Annual dinner, 3 items (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0235 - RL11552-OP-0237)
        - 2009 Annual dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0204)
        - 2009 Annual dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0207)
        - 2009 Annual dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0274)
        - 2010 Annual dinner and historical photographs (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0224)
        - 2010 Annual dinner and historical photographs (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0257)
        - 2011 Annual dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0260)
        - 2011 Annual dinner Shevry Lassiter (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0259)
        - 2012 Annual gala and Board meeting (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0210)
        - 2013 Annual gala dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0267)
        - 40th Anniversary gala annual dinner, 2010 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0219)
        - 40th Anniversary gala annual dinner, disk 1-5, 2010; 5 items (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0262 - RL11552-OP-0266)
        - Annual dinner, 2005 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0071)
        - Annual dinner, 2007 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0115)
        - Annual dinner, 2009 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0187)
        - Annual dinner 300dpi images disc 1, 2002 Mar 26 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0374)
        - Annual dinner 300dpi images disc 2, 2002 Mar 26 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0375)
        - Annual dinner 72dpi images disc 1, 2002 Mar 26 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0376)
        - Annual dinner 72dpi images disc 2, 2002 Mar 26 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0377)
        - Annual dinner Images, 2005 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0222)
        - Annual dinner images 1-331, 2006; 4 items (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0054 - RL11552-OP-0057)
        - Annual dinner raw images disc 1, 2002 Mar 26 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0372)
        - Annual dinner raw images disc 2, 2002 Mar 26 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0373)
        - Annual dinner, disk 1-2, 2012 May 1; 2 items (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0247 - RL11552-OP-0248)
        - Annual dinner, historical Photographs, 2010 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0060)
        - Annual gala dinner, 2012 May 1 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0069)
        - Annual gala dinner, 2013 May 7 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0113)
        - Annual Louis E. Martin Award dinner, 2009 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0203)
        - Archived FOCUS issues, 1972-2007 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0244)
        - Asset Building in Low-Income Communities of Color, undated (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0249)
        - Balancing smart metering with consumer interests, 2010 Dec 10 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0190)
        - Bioterrorism report briefing, 2004 Sep 14 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0371)
        - Blackout tech policy forum, 2010 Dec 16 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0226)
        - Blackout technology policy forum, 2010 Dec 16 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0216)
        - Blackout technology policy forum, 2010 Dec 16 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0228)
        - Board meeting and annual gala dinner, 2012 May 1 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0114)
        - Board of governors meeting, 2005 Sep (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0379)
        - Board of Governors meeting, 2005 Sep 28 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0127)
        - Board of Governors meeting, 2010 Jul 13 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0269)
        - Braintrust Closing the Wealth Gap, 2010 Sep 23 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0200)
        - Broadband in Rural Areas, Health and Wellness Dialogues, Economic Security, 2009 Sep 25 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0246)
        - Building a Healthy Economy: Creating Employment Opportunity and Equity, 2013 Apr 4 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0157)
        - C. Naylor, VP Development, 2003 May 9 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0073)
        - Capitol Visitors Center, disk 1-2, 2010 Apr 14; 2 items (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0191 - RL11552-OP-0192)
        - Capitol Visitors Center, disk 1-2, 2010 Apr 14; 2 items (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0252 - RL11552-OP-0253)
        - CEAC Speaker series, 2010 Oct 26 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0250)
        - CEAC Speaker Series, 2010 Oct 26 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0326)
        - CEAC Speakers Series, 2010 Oct (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0270)
        - Charity Golf Classic, 2004 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0179)
        - Climate Change, 2008 Jul 29 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0277)
        - Climate Change, undated (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0327)
        - Climate change and the EPA, 2009 Feb 12 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0245)
        - Climate Change Commissioner's Retreat, 2010 Mar 9-10 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0272)
        - Climate Change Critical Speakers Series, 2010 Jul 27 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0271)
        - Climate Change Kickoff Commissioner Headshots, 2008 Jul (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0335)
        - Climate Change photos, 2008 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0403)
        - Climate Change photos, 2008 Jul 28 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0405)
        - Climate Change photos, 2008 Jul 29; 2 items (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0406 - RL11552-OP-0407)
        - Climate, headshot, 2008 Jan; Sep (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0276)
        - Closing the Wealth Gap, 2009 Jun 29 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0198)
        - Closing the Wealth Gap, undated (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0268)
        - Commission to Engage African Americans on Climate Change, 2011 Sep 20 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0153)
        - Commission to Engage African Americans on Climate Change, 2011 Sep 20 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0164)
        - Commission to Engage African Americans on Climate Change, 2011 Sep 20 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0165)
        - Commission to Engage African Americans on Climate Change, 2011 Sep 20 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0173)
        - Congressional Black Caucus annual legislative weekend events, 2009 Sep 21-23 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0242)
        - Congressional Black Caucus annual legislative weekend events, 2009 Sep 25 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0243)
        - Congressional Black Caucus Braintrust Closing the Wealth Gap, 2009 Sep 23 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0202)
        - Congressional Black Caucus Health Braintrust, 2008 Sep 26 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0082)
        - Conunser Protection event, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0077)
        - Critical Issues in Climate Change Speakers Series, 2010 Jul 27 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0178)
        - Critical Issues in Climate Change Speakers Series The Green Economy and Clean Energy, 2010 Jun 17 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0258)
        - Critical Issues in Climate Change Symposium, 2010 Sep 17 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0212)
        - David Chavern and Norma Asnes, 2009 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0239)
        - DC Forum, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0076)
        - Dinner, 2004 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0160)
        - Eddie Williams Corporate Portrait, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0074)
        - Eleanor Farrar (2 discs), undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0133)
        - Emerging Leaders, 2005 Apr 20 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0383)
        - Gala, undated (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0254)
        - Global Climate Justice Roundtable, Disc 1, 2011 Sep 21 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0158)
        - Global Climate Justice Roundtable, Disc 2, 2011 Sep 21 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0159)
        - Governance Planning forum and dinner, 2008 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0278)
        - Headshot, New Orleans, media and technology, 2008 Jan; Mar; Nov (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0234)
        - Health care summit, 2009 Sep 17 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0241)
        - Health forum, 2009 Sep 25 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0134)
        - Health Policy Institute, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0079)
        - Institute on Civic Engagement and Governance, 2011 Nov 18 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0230)
        - Interns and President Williams, 2001 Jul 13 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0184)
        - IP Broadband Event, 2013 Feb 13 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0280)
        - JCPES, 2008 Oct 2 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0080)
        - JCPES 2009 annual dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0206)
        - JCPES and NPC, 2003 May 14 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0171)
        - JCPES dinner, Disc 1-2, 2003 Apr 14 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0063)
        - JCPES dinner, Disc 2, 2003 Apr 14 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0064)
        - JCPES Images 0001-0112, Disc 1-2, 2004 Apr 21 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0065)
        - JCPES Images 0114-0231, Disc 2, 2004 Apr 21 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0066)
        - JCPES, The Ritz Carlton, 2008 Feb 26 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0273)
        - Joint Center, 2010 Jul 13 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0256)
        - Joint Center 2009 annual dinner (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0205)
        - Joint Center annual dinner and historical photographs, 2010 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0062)
        - Joint Center annual Report and historic photographs, 2009 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0339)
        - Joint Center Board of Governors meeting, 2012 May 1 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0211)
        - Joint Center dinner, 2005 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0070)
        - Joint Center dinner, 2006 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0053)
        - Joint Center dinner, 2005 Apr 20 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0167)
        - Joint Center Employees, 2011 Jul 28 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0217)
        - Joint Center Fundraiser, 2004 Sep (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0132)
        - Joint Center gala, 2011 May 3 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0261)
        - Joint Center General Reception and dinner, 2004 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0067)
        - Joint Center historical Photographs, 2010 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0058)
        - Joint Center Staff, 2010 Jun 14 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0072)
        - Joint Center staff, 2010 Jun 14 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0220)
        - Joint Center staff photographs, 2011 Jul 28 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0232)
        - Joint Center's annual dinner, disk 2, 2009 Apr 21 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0208)
        - Joint Congressional briefing: Climate Change and 2010 Midterm Election, 2010 Apr 14 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0177)
        - Kasim Reed at annual gala and Board meeting, 2012 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0061)
        - Kasim Reed at annual gala and Board meeting, 2012 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0068)
        - Louis E. Martin Great American Award, 2003 Apr 14 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0139)
        - MBRT and AT&T press conference, 2001 Sep 26 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0380)
        - Media and Technology Institute Climate Change Commission Media and Technology Luncheon National Working Group, 2009 Sep 21-23 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0231)
        - Media and Technology Institute, disk 1-2, forum, 2009 Sep 21; 3 items (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0193 - RL11552-OP-0195)
        - Minorities and The National Broadband Plan, 2011 Mar 1 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0251)
        - MTI - Smart Grid, 2010 Oct 5 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0197)
        - National Black Caucus disc 1, 2006 Jan 20 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0381)
        - National Black Caucus disc 2, 2006 Jan 20 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0382)
        - Naylor 4357, 4358, 4359, 2003 Nov 2; 3 items (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0129 - RL11552-OP-0131)
        - Old Joint Center photographs, 2005-2009 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0059)
        - Opinion poll briefing, 2004 Oct 19 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0378)
        - Paternal Commission briefing, 2010 May 20 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0325)
        - Photo - MBRT/AT&T Press conference, 2001 Sep 26 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0181)
        - Photos by year, 2006 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0223)
        - Place Matters Action Lab, 2013 Jul 10-11 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0156)
        - Place Matters national conference, 2011 Sep 7 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0218)
        - Place Matters, disk 1, 2011 Sep 7 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0175)
        - Place Matters, disk 2, 2011 Sep 7 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0176)
        - Portrait shots Ralph B. Everett, 2006 Nov 28 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0227)
        - Post 9/11 conference, 2002 Jan 15 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0161)
        - Post Presidential Election Reflections, 2008 Nov 5 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0255)
        - Post_Election forum, 2012 Nov 7 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0214)
        - Ralph Everett Headshots, 2006 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0213)
        - Redistricting 1992-2002 Voting Rights and Minority Representation, 2002 May 22 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0128)
        - Reproductive Health for Young Men of Color, 2006 Sep 27 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0275)
        - Rev. Jesse Jackson, 2009 Nov 18 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0225)
        - Rev. Jesse Jackson luncheon, 2009 Nov 18 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0240)
        - Samuel DeWitt Proctor conference visit, 2009 Mar 27 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0152)
        - Sequestration Panel Discussion Event, 2013 Feb 28 (Box 40, Disk RL11552-OP-0322)
        - Smart Grid, 2010 Oct 5 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0196)
        - State of the Union Watch Party, 2012 Jan 24 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0209)
        - Strategic Black Officers, 2010 May 18 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0174)
        - The 2010 Midterm Elections: Implications for African Americans and Other Communities of Color, 2010 Nov 16 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0229)
        - The Black Women's Agenda meeting, 2008 Sep 26 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0081)
        - The Joint Center part at the Remi Restaurant, 2006 Feb 10 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0136)
        - The New Digital Profile, 2001 Jul 26 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0215)
        - The Wealth Gap Policy forum, 2009 Jun 29 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0201)
        - Tony Iton, Panel of Be Loud group shots, 2012 Mar (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0075)
        - unlabelled, 2004 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0112)
        - Unlabelled conference, 2001 Apr 6 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0189)
        - Unlabelled JCPES, 2006 Apr 11 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0141)
        - Unlabelled meeting, 2009 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0188)
        - Verizon, dinner (Leslie), Unnatural Cause, post-election, 2008 Mar; Apr; Nov (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0238)
        - Victor Holt, 2008 Jan 17 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0233)
        - W. Clark, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0078)
        - Wealth Gap Policy forum, 2009 Jun 29 (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0199)
      - OCM Computer files, 1972-2011
        - Dinner Logos, Photoshop, jpegs, 2004 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0083)
        - Dinner Logos and jpegs, 2004 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0084)
        - Raw files, 2003 Apr 12 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0085)
        - New jointcenter.org, 2005 Jan 26 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0086)
        - Mac format files, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0087)
        - Final files, 2007 Feb 21 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0088)
        - New Joint Center website, 2005 Jan 13 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0089)
        - Desktop and New jointcenter.org, 2004 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0090)
        - Final pdf of focus NL, 2006 Jan-Feb (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0091)
        - HPI/Place Matters files, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0092)
        - PDFs, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0093)
        - Joint Center 4th Report, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0094)
        - New Joint Center web, 2004 Jan 11 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0095)
        - PDFs, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0096)
        - Pictures on Liselle's computer, 2005 Jun 16 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0097)
        - FOCUS mag, 1972-1996 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0098)
        - Final Files, 2004 Nov 29 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0099)
        - Final Files and PDFs, 2004 May 19 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0100)
        - Final Files, 2007 Jan 5 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0101)
        - FOCUS pdf's, 1972-2007 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0102)
        - Gina's Backup, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0103)
        - files, excels, records, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0104)
        - New Joint Center web graphics, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0105)
        - Master file REQ, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0106)
        - Mac DVD player installer, 2006 Jul 7 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0107)
        - Trends in Child Health PDFs and inDesign projects, 2010 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0108)
        - Place Matters Conference Fact Sheets and Presentations, 2011 Sep 7 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0109)
        - Slides about Medicaid, 2005 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0117)
        - Windows Media Installer, 2003 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0118)
        - DVD Player Updates, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0119)
        - Logos, 2005 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0120)
        - PSD files, 2005 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0121)
        - FOCUS magazine, 2007 May-Jun (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0122)
        - Medicaid Graphics, 2005 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0123)
        - Joint Center Graphics for Place Matters, 2012 Jun (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0124)
        - Food and Fitness website graphics, 2008 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0126)
        - Redistricting and Voting Rights graphics, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0135)
        - FOCUS Files, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0137)
        - Joint Center book graphics, 2004 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0138)
        - The Burden of the War in Iraq roundtable presentations and documents, 2007 Mar 20 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0140)
        - Annual dinner materials, 2006 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0142)
        - Kelly, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0143)
        - Art Marco files, 2007 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0144)
        - Military Roundtable presentations and audio, 2006 Nov 6 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0145)
        - Annual dinner materials, 2006 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0146)
        - Annual Report materials, 2004 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0147)
        - Federal Page and Commercial Appeal PDFs, 2004 Jul 29; Aug 23 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0148)
        - Using Maps to Promote Health Equity materials, 2009 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0149)
        - Healthcare Summit, 2009 Sep 17 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0150)
        - Archived FOCUS Magazine Issues, 1972-2007 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0154)
        - Archived FOCUS Magazine Issues, 1972-2007 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0155)
        - Master file REQ, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0162)
        - unidentified file, undated (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0166)
        - HPI Executive Summary materials, 2005 (Box 19, Disk RL11552-OP-0168)
        - HPI Notepad and Business Cards materials, undated (Box 39, Disk RL11552-OP-0169)